Guide to the Jimmy De Sana Papers 1954-1997 (bulk 1977-1990) MSS 202
© 2010 Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series V: Negatives by project
  - Subseries B: Submission
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS SandM #8
    - Title: (Box 52)
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “Beach, Harness”
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “SandM, Cigarette Torture”
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “SandM, Cover Plus*”
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “SandM, Cover and Tits”
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “SandM, Cover #1 and Closet
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “SandM, Enema and Rope”
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “Enema”
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “SandM, Flame Cock - Shower (Spread)” and also “Snare Kit Toes”
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “SandM, Harris #1”
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “SandM, Harris #3”
      Number of Items: 175
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “SandM, Legs Sep, Etc.”
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “SandM, Water Sp, Tube, Etc”
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “SandM, Masking Tape”
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “SandM, RBR, Sofa”
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “SandM, LBR Sofa”
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “RBR, 2CV, Tits”
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “RBR, Tits, Porch, Shoulder”
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “SandM, Saluki”
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “SandM, Seven Gates, Scissors, Whip”
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “Ship and Clothes Pins, SandM”
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “SandM, Ship and Posing”
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “SandM, Bondage #1 with Nylon String”
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “SandM, String #2”
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “WS, Bondage”
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “Water Sports 1050 TV SM”
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “Water Sports, Tub, Spread Prep”
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “SandM, Terry” Terence Sellers Model
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “Toilet”
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “SandM, Trunk, Car”
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “Car and Harness, SandM”
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “SandM, TV”
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “SandM, WS Kitchen, Shower Bondage”
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS SandM RS and Nikkorex
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “AA Robert Crispo”
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “Ass Plug and Whip Plug”
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS "Byron's Cock with Dr. Goss' Mouth Model"
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “RS - Candle and Ball Sep”
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “RS - Candle Etc”
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “Crucifix, Piercing, Vaginal Sep, Tina, Four Shoes, SWK”
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “Mock TV and Crucifix”
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “Dog Collar”
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “Egypt”
    - Title: (Box 52)
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “Enema, Head Shots, Shaving”
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “Enema (Sink) W.S. (Roof)”
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “WS - Steps”
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “Female Posing Strip”
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “Woman, WS Tube, Sofa Bondage, Shoe Fetish”
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “Woman Sofa Shackles
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “Feme, Posing, Spank”
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “Woman Make Up, Slave Dressing”
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “Woman Refrigerator, TV, Posing”
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “Fist Fuck #2, Ass Sep #2”
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “Fist Fuck #1, Wax #2”
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS "Flash Self"
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: "Fly Paper Fly Swatter"
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “Fly Swatter, Laced Hands, Tit Clamps”
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “Jeff Overdorf”
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “Jonas”
      Number of Items: 99
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “RS SM Mirror Dildo”
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “Penis Torture”
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “Piercing”
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “Piss, Wine Glass, and Iron”
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “Foot Fuck, Leash, Scat #2”
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “Scat, Rubber Sheets”
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “Rubber Sheet, Posing, and Boot Fetish”
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “Shower Self”
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “Final Shower Spread, Fist Fuck #2 Mirror”
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “Extention Cord, Shower #2, Reshoot Whip Ass”
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “Spot”
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “Suicide - Final”
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “Mock Suicide, Boot Fetish, Pose with Tits”
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “Suicide”
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “Terrace, Toilet, Contact Paper, Jeff S”
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “Jeff S, Jock Strap, Vaginal Separator #1”
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “Jeff S, Terrace, Window”
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “SandM, Trunk - Preliminary”
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “Whip, Carpet, Toilet”
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “Tube up Ass / Posing / Toilet”
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “Iron, Bubble, Enema”
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “Water Sports, Coney #1”
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “Enema in Carafe, Condom #1, Whip”
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “Contracept, Whip”
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “Ass Plug, Wine Glass #2”
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “Wine Glass #2 ”
  - Subseries C: Early Sex
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Athletic Tape
      Process: 4x5 Negative
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: "Balloons shoot Model Darrell Bagley"
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: "Casters shoot Labeled by JDS “Alex, Wheels/Feet”"
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Coat Hanger shoot
    - Title:, 1984 (Box 52)
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Giant Beachball
      Process: 3x5 Negative
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Iguana
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS "Infra-Nudes (Tub)"
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Mirror Beachball
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Nude and chair
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Pool rephotographed
    - Title: (Box 52)
    - Title:, 1984 (Box 52)
      Description: Slinkies
  - Subseries D: $bfat
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: "Sweatshirt and Dog Darrell Bagley model"
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Shoot like Bubble Gum
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Dalmation at Beach
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Cowboy Hat shoot
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Pants Shoot
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “Sweatshirt (Dog), Twin Pants, Two in Sweatshirt (Stairs)”
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: On the Beach with Jimmy Jr.
      Process: 8x10 Negative
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Pants Puppy
    - Title:, 1984 (Box 52)
  - Subseries E: $dobjects
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Original Slide Sleeve
      Process: Original Slide Sleeve
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Abstract composition
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Black Cat Shoot
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Cones
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Labeled by JDS "Mutilated Objects"
    - Title: (Box 52)
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Pyramid
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Rings
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Seed Pods
    - Title: (Box 52)
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Number of Items: 108
    - Title: (Box 52)
      Description: Opium Weights
    - Title: (Box 52)
  - Subseries F: Cut Up
    - Title: (Box 53)
      Description: Flour, Eggs, Q - Tips, Tape
    - Title: (Box 53)
      Description: Pendant and other Portrait Variations
  - Subseries G: Auto-Portrait
    - Title: (Box 53)
      Description: "Aluminum Foil shoot Marilyn"
    - Title: (Box 53)
      Description: "Birds, Cardboard, Seated Tuxedo "
    - Title: (Box 53)
    - Title: (Box 53)
      Description: "Cellophane Tape Labeled by JDS “Mona”"
    - Title: (Box 53)
      Description: Earring Shoot
    - Title: (Box 53)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “Self - Flour”
    - Title: (Box 53)
      Description: Pizza Crust Re-photographed
    - Title: (Box 53)
      Number of Items: 41
    - Title: (Box 53)
      Description: Q-tips
    - Title: (Box 53)
      Description: Shoot for Cap
    - Title: (Box 53)
      Description: Shoot for Scar
    - Title: Smoke, 1985 (Box 53)
    - Title: Smoke, 1985 (Box 53)
    - Title: (Box 53)
      Description: Tape
- Series VI: Negatives by theme
  Items from the Portrait theme (subseries H) are organized by the subject's last name. Where a last name is absent slides are organized alphabetically by first name. These are followed by unidentified subjects.
  Subseries K contains medium-format negatives which could not be stored with the bulk of the negatives in this series. They are organized into sub-subseries which correspond to the thematic break-down of the rest of Series VI. (ie. the Portrait theme recurs in both)
  - Subseries A: Documentation
    - Title: (Box 53)
      Description: Rope, Labeled by JDS here "Original - Suicide”
  - Subseries B: Early Work
    - Title: (Box 53)
      Description: Christ Statues
    - Title: (Box 53)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “2 Houses”
    - Title: (Box 53)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “Flash, Nativity, Sub. Houses”
    - Title: (Box 53)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “Flash, Sub. Houses”
    - Title: (Box 53)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “Travel / Nature / Stef”
    - Title: (Box 53)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “Nature - Stef. Mother's House”
  - Subseries C: Events
    - Title: (Box 53)
      Description: Anna Sui Party
    - Title:, 1973 (Box 53)
      Description: Avant Garde Festival
    - Title: (Box 53)
    - Title: (Box 53)
    - Title: (Box 53)
      Description: Coney Island candid shots
    - Title: (Box 53)
      Description: Cortez Party
    - Title: (Box 53)
      Description: Critic's Conference
    - Title: (Box 53)
      Description: Duncan Hannah Party
    - Title: (Box 53)
      Description: Event at Stefanotti Gallery
    - Title: (Box 53)
      Description: Fashion Show
    - Title: (Box 53)
      Description: Halloween Party
    - Title: (Box 53)
      Description: Labeled by JDS "Action News"
      Number of Items: 109
    - Title: (Box 53)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “Bleeker Bob and CBGB”
    - Title: (Box 53)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “Buddah University”
    - Title: (Box 53)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “Carey Inauguration - Albany”
    - Title: (Box 53)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “Casa de Las Americas (demonstration)”
    - Title: (Box 53)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “Fashion Show”
    - Title: (Box 53)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “Ft Greene Flash and Flash Self”
    - Title: (Box 53)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “Museum of Broadcasting, #1”
      Number of Items: 68
    - Title: (Box 53)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “Gregory - Palm Beach - Mary Lea”
    - Title: (Box 53)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “Perless”
      Number of Items: 73
    - Title: (Box 53)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “Rocky Horror”
    - Title: (Box 53)
      Description: Loft
    - Title:, 1981 (Box 53)
      Description: New York New Wave
    - Title: (Box 53)
      Description: New York, Puerto Rican Liberation Protest
    - Title: (Box 53)
      Description: Opening
      Number of Items: 126
    - Title: (Box 53)
      Description: Opening - John Giorno
    - Title: (Box 53)
      Description: Opening - New Museum, Marcia Tucker
    - Title: (Box 53)
      Description: Party - Labelled by JDS "1050 PTY"
    - Title: (Box 53)
      Description: Press Conference
    - Title: (Box 53)
      Description: Reinhardt Onnasch Party
    - Title: (Box 53)
      Description: Robert Steffanotti Party
    - Title: (Box 53)
      Description: Robert Stefanotti and Saluki
    - Title: (Box 53)
      Description: SOHO Saturday
    - Title: (Box 53)
      Description: Tea Dance
    - Title: (Box 53)
      Description: Zapatas Parole
    - Title: (Box 53)
      Description: Unknown Events
    - Title: (Box 53)
      Number of Items: 365
  - Subseries D: Landscape
    - Title: (Box 53)
  - Subseries E: Miscellaneous
    - Title: (Box 53)
      Description: Air Force Carrier
    - Title: (Box 53)
      Description: Brooch
    - Title: (Box 53)
      Description: Cat and Mouse
    - Title: (Box 53)
      Description: Dalmatian and Play Money
    - Title: (Box 53)
    - Title: (Box 53)
    - Title: (Box 53)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “Infra Red"
    - Title: (Box 53)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “Spotted Dog) A”
    - Title: (Box 53)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “Spotted Dog - Pup?) B”
    - Title: (Box 53)
      Description: Motorcycles
    - Title: (Box 53)
    - Title: (Box 53)
      Description: Television
    - Title: (Box 53)
      Description: Uknown object
    - Title: (Box 53)
      Description: Walk up Apartment and Loft
  - Subseries F: Nudes
    - Title: (Box 53)
      Description: Foot and Penis
  - Subseries G: Paper Collage
    - Title: (Box 53)
      Description: Desire
    - Title: (Box 53)
      Description: Forget Me Not
    - Title: (Box 53)
      Description: Labeled by JDS “Language Collage”
    - Title: (Box 53)
    - Title: (Box 53)
    - Title: (Box 53)
      Description: Variations - collage
      Number of Items: 785
  - Subseries H: Portraits
    - Title: (Box 54)
      Description: Acker, Kathy
    - Title: (Box 54)
    - Title: (Box 54)
      Number of Items: 119
    - Title: (Box 54)
      Number of Items: 194
    - Title: (Box 54)
      Description: Belle MC
      Number of Items: 82
    - Title: (Box 54)
      Description: Brams, Peter
      Number of Items: 187
    - Title: (Box 54)
      Description: Brecht, George; Higgins, Dick; Dienes, Sari; Fitzgibbon, Colen; Alison; Watts, Bob - labeled by JDS
    - Title: (Box 54)
      Description: Battcock, Gregory; Varbie, Stephen - labeled by JDS
    - Title: (Box 54)
      Description: Battcock Cover - labeled by JDS, also Ronnie Cutrone
    - Title: (Box 54)
      Description: Blondie - labeled by JDS
    - Title: (Box 54)
      Description: Bomb - labeled by JDS
    - Title: (Box 54)
      Description: Bourdon, David with Robert Rosenblum, Jane Kaplowitz
    - Title: (Box 54)
      Description: Bronson, AA with Diego Cortez, Anya Phillips, Edwardo Hidalgo
    - Title: (Box 54)
      Description: Bronson, AA, Moda, Etc - Labeled by JDS
      Number of Items: 74
    - Title: (Box 54)
      Description: Bronson, AA;, Mark Krayenhoff
    - Title: (Box 54)
      Description: Burnin Skies - labeled by JDS
    - Title: (Box 54)
      Description: Burroughs, William S - labeled by JDS
    - Title: (Box 54)
      Description: Burroughs, William; Cortez, Diego- labeled by JDS also with Acconci, Vito
    - Title: (Box 54)
      Description: Byrne, David - labeled by JDS
    - Title: (Box 54)
      Description: Byrne, David with Mich, Sham, Richard, Tobias, Liza, Michael, Betsy - labeled by JDS
    - Title: (Box 54)
      Description: Byron - labeled by JDS
    - Title: (Box 54)
      Description: Byron, Black Pants - labeled by JDS
    - Title: (Box 54)
      Description: Cage, John - labeled by JDS
    - Title: (Box 54)
      Description: Chance, James
    - Title: (Box 54)
      Description: Churicova, Inna; Panfilov, Gleb; "Russian Film" - labeled by JDS
    - Title: (Box 54)
      Description: Clarence
      Number of Items: 207
    - Title: (Box 54)
    - Title: (Box 54)
      Description: Cortez, Bradley; various NY - labeled by JDS
      Number of Items: 92
    - Title: (Box 54)
    - Title: (Box 54)
    - Title: (Box 54)
      Description: Crutchfield, Robin - labeled by JDS
      Number of Items: 244
    - Title: (Box 54)
      Description: Cutrone, Ronnie; Cale, John - labeled by JDS
    - Title: (Box 54)
      Description: Dali, Salvador, and Gregory Battcock shoot
      Number of Items: 81
    - Title: (Box 54)
      Description: de Sana, Jimmy; Phillips, Anya; White, James Chance; Cortez; Diego
      Number of Items: 140
    - Title: (Box 54)
      Description: de Sana, Jimmy and Edwardo Hidalgo on MTA
    - Title: (Box 54)
      Description: de Sana, Jimmy with Byron
    - Title: (Box 54)
    - Title: (Box 54)
      Description: Dead Boys
    - Title: (Box 54)
      Description: Delight, Duka - labeled by JDS "Duka, Eddie, Katerina"
    - Title: (Box 54)
      Description: Diodes
    - Title: (Box 54)
      Description: Dog Flash - labeled by JDS
    - Title: (Box 54)
    - Title: (Box 54)
      Description: Ensley, Susan
    - Title: (Box 54)
      Description: Erasers
    - Title: (Box 54)
      Description: Evy
    - Title: (Box 54)
      Description: Fine, Albert Great Neck - labeled by JDS
    - Title: (Box 54)
      Description: Fine, Albert with Michael Cooper, Ray Johnson, and Coney Island
    - Title: (Box 54)
      Description: Fine, Albert, Building Crack Up - labeled by JDS
    - Title: (Box 54)
      Description: Fisher, Norman; Cortez, Diego; Hidalgo, Edward; Jose; Jessica - labeled by JDS
    - Title: (Box 54)
      Description: Fleshtones
    - Title: (Box 55)
      Description: Geldzahler, Henry; Kornblee, Jill - labeled by JDS
    - Title: (Box 55)
      Description: Giorno, John book opening - labeled by JDS
    - Title: (Box 55)
      Description: Gould, Tom - labeled by JDS
    - Title: (Box 55)
      Description: Gordon, Robert; Goldberg, Jeff - Labeled by JDS
    - Title: (Box 55)
      Description: Greathouse, Timothy
    - Title: (Box 55)
    - Title: (Box 55)
      Description: Greif, Paula - labeled by JDS
    - Title: (Box 55)
      Description: Hannah, Duncan; Nylon, Judy / "Duncan's Opening" labeled by JDS
    - Title: (Box 55)
      Description: Hell, Richard - labeled by JDS
    - Title: (Box 55)
      Description: Heller, Joan; Kew Gardens - labeled by JDS
    - Title: (Box 55)
      Description: Hidalgo, Eddie with YSL, Bill Blass, and Billy Baldwin - labeled by JDS
    - Title: (Box 55)
    - Title: (Box 55)
      Description: Hidalgo, Edwardo and Duncan, Hannah
    - Title: (Box 55)
      Description: Hidalgo, Edwardo; Phillips, Anya; Cortez, Diego; David "EB" - labeled by JDS
    - Title: (Box 55)
      Description: "Hitler" Nude
    - Title: (Box 55)
      Description: Idol, Billy; Battcock, Gregory - labeled by JDS
    - Title: (Box 55)
      Description: Incandela, Gerald
    - Title: (Box 55)
      Description: Johnson, Ray with May Wilson, Marie Stilkmo, and Copies Polaroid - labeled by JDS
    - Title: (Box 55)
      Description: Johnson, Ray, and others
    - Title: (Box 55)
      Description: Johnson, Ray's Buddahgraphs, Violin Shop, Bucky and Leo - labeled by JDS
    - Title: (Box 55)
      Description: Johnson, Susan
    - Title: (Box 55)
      Description: Levine, Palestine, SMK - labeled by JDS
    - Title: (Box 55)
      Description: Lido; Bleeker Bob's - labeled by JDS
    - Title: (Box 55)
      Description: Lindsay, John, etc - labeled by JDS
    - Title: (Box 55)
    - Title: (Box 55)
      Description: Losta, Christin
    - Title: (Box 55)
      Description: Margit - labeled by JDS
    - Title: (Box 55)
      Description: Mars; Hell, Richard - labeled by JDS
    - Title: (Box 55)
      Description: McCormick, Carlo; Hughes-Freeland, Tessa
    - Title: (Box 55)
      Description: Mc Dermit, David - labeled by JDS
    - Title: (Box 55)
      Description: Gioia - labeled by JDS
    - Title: (Box 55)
      Description: Miguel, Kenny Scharf, and Tony Schfrazi
    - Title: (Box 55)
      Description: Mille - labeled by JDS
    - Title: (Box 55)
      Description: Miss, Jane - labeled by JDS
      Number of Items: 80
    - Title: (Box 55)
      Description: Mitchell, Eric - labeled by JDS
      Number of Items: 117
    - Title: (Box 55)
      Description: Mitchell, Eric; Eric's Film - labeled by JDS
    - Title: (Box 55)
      Description: Mumps - labeled by JDS
    - Title: (Box 55)
      Description: Necessaries - labeled by JDS
      Number of Items: 52
    - Title: (Box 55)
      Description: Nervous Wrecks - labeled by JDS
    - Title: (Box 55)
      Description: New Wave - labeled by JDS
    - Title: (Box 55)
      Description: Jane Nisselson - labeled by JDS
    - Title: (Box 55)
      Number of Items: 116
    - Title: (Box 55)
      Description: Nylon, Judy - labeled by JDS
    - Title: (Box 56)
    - Title: (Box 56)
      Description: Poe, Amos
    - Title: (Box 56)
      Description: Ramos, Jose
    - Title: (Box 56)
      Description: Resnick, Marcia - labeled by JDS
    - Title: (Box 56)
      Description: Resnick party - labeled by JDS
      Number of Items: 98
    - Title: (Box 56)
      Description: Rico - labeled by JDS
      Number of Items: 165
    - Title: (Box 56)
      Description: Rico and Hands - labeled by JDS
    - Title: (Box 56)
      Description: Rivers, Larry; Elaine, Charles Fahlen, Hal Bromm, Valerie, Colette - labeled by JDS
    - Title: (Box 56)
      Description: Rolf - labeled by JDS
      Number of Items: 164
    - Title: (Box 56)
      Description: Rose, Frank - labeled by JDS
    - Title: (Box 56)
    - Title: (Box 56)
      Description: Schiff, Leslie
      Number of Items: 105
    - Title: (Box 56)
      Description: "Sebastian #1 - labeled by JDS Labeled in prints as “Ron”"
    - Title: (Box 56)
      Description: "Sebastian #2 - labeled by JDS Labeled in prints as “Ron”"
    - Title: (Box 56)
      Description: "Sebastian #3 - labeled by JDS Labeled in prints as “Ron”"
    - Title: (Box 56)
      Description: "Sebastian #4 - labeled by JDS Labeled in prints as “Ron”"
    - Title: (Box 56)
      Description: "Sebastian #5 - labeled by JDS Labeled in prints as “Ron”"
    - Title: (Box 56)
      Description: "Sebastian #6 - labeled by JDS Labeled in prints as “Ron”"
    - Title: (Box 56)
      Description: "Sebastian #7 - labeled by JDS Labeled in prints as “Ron”"
    - Title: (Box 56)
      Description: Sellers, Terence; Hannah, Duncan
      Number of Items: 269
    - Title: (Box 56)
      Description: Smith, Jack's apartment - labeled by JDS
    - Title: (Box 56)